♪
( Eugeo sighs )
( girl sighs )
HELLO.
WE ARE--I MEAN...
I AM FIZEL, A SISTER-IN-TRAINING
OF THE CHURCH.
HOW DO?
AND THIS TIMID LITTLE THING
IS MY FELLOW SISTER-IN-TRAINING.
Linel: UH, I’M LINEL.
Fizel: WE HEARD
THERE WERE INTRUDERS
FROM THE DARK TERRITORY
LURKING ABOUT.
ARE YOU THEY?
Eugeo: HUH?
Kirito: I THINK
I’LL LET YOU HANDLE THIS ONE.
THEY LOOK ANNOYING.
( Eugeo sighs )
UM, WE ARE, SORT OF.
WE’RE ACTUALLY
FROM THE HUMAN REALM,
NOT THE DARK TERRITORY.
AS FOR INTRUDING HERE,
I GUESS WE ARE, TECHNICALLY.
( girls sigh )
Fizel: WELL, NEL? DO THESE TWO
LOOK ANYTHING
LIKE MONSTERS TO YOU? HUH?
WHERE ARE
THEIR HORNS AND TAILS?
Linel: BUT HOW SHOULD I KNOW?
I WAS JUST TELLING YOU WHAT
THE BOOK SAID THEY LOOKED LIKE.
YOU’RE THE ONE
JUMPING TO CONCLUSIONS, ZEL.
Eugeo: UH, LADIES...
WE’LL GO.
IF SOMEONE SEES US,
YOU’LL GET IN TROUBLE.
( girls giggle )
Fizel: DON’T WORRY. THERE’S
NO CHANCE OF THAT HAPPENING.
THIS MORNING, THE CHURCH ORDERED
ALL THE MONKS, NUNS,
AND APPRENTICES
TO STAY IN THEIR QUARTERS
AND LOCK THEIR DOORS.
THIS WAS THE PERFECT OPPORTUNITY
FOR US TO SNEAK OUT
AND HAVE A LOOK
AT THESE NASTY INTRUDERS.
EH? ( grunts )
HUH.
( Eugeo sighs )
Fizel: THEY’RE HUMAN.
- Linel: YES, VERY.
- ( Eugeo chuckles )
Linel: WE HEARD
YOU WERE ARRESTED,
BUT BROKE YOUR SPIRITUAL CHAINS
AND ESCAPED.
WE ALSO HEARD YOU DEFEATED
TWO INTEGRITY KNIGHTS.
THAT’S WHY I WAS SURE
YOU WERE MONSTERS
FROM THE DARK TERRITORY,
EITHER THAT
OR KNIGHTS OF DARKNESS.
I’M SURE YOU CAN UNDERSTAND WHY
WE WERE SO CURIOUS ABOUT YOU.
( Eugeo sighs ) HUH?
Linel: ONE LAST THING,
DO YOU MIND TELLING US
WHAT YOUR NAMES ARE?
Eugeo: EH, NOT AT ALL.
I’M EUGEO,
AND THIS HERE IS KIRITO.
- ( Kirito groans )
- Linel: HUH.
DO YOU NOT HAVE LAST NAMES?
Eugeo: NO.
MY FAMILY ARE SETTLERS.
AND DO YOU HAVE LAST NAMES?
Linel: YES. WE’VE BEEN WAITING
TO SHARE THEM WITH YOU.
Eugeo: UH...
- ( blade stabs )
- ( groaning )
Linel: MY FULL NAME, SINNER,
IS LINEL SYNTHESIS TWENTY-EIGHT.
( singing in Japanese )
♪
♪ PROUD OF MYSELF ♪
( Eugeo gasping )
( Kirito gasps ) EUGE--
- ( blade stabs )
- ( groaning )
( Fizel chuckles ) MY NAME
IS FIZEL SYNTHESIS TWENTY-NINE.
Eugeo: YOU’RE A...
INTEGRI...
( both groan )
Linel: DON’T FRET,
EUGEO WITHOUT-A-LAST-NAME.
YOU’RE OURS NOW.
( footsteps shuffling )
( Eugeo grunting )
Linel: IT’S A PARALYSIS POISON.
WE DON’T WANT YOU TO DIE YET,
NOT UNTIL WE GET YOU
TO THE 50th FLOOR, ANYWAY.
I’M SURE
YOU MUST BE WONDERING...
"HOW IN THE WORLD
DID THESE TWO LITTLE GIRLS
BECOME INTEGRITY KNIGHTS?"
( Eugeo gasping )
Linel: WE WERE BORN AND RAISED
INSIDE THE CENTRAL CATHEDRAL.
ONE DAY, ADMINISTRATOR HERSELF
ORDERED THE MONKS AND NUNS HERE
TO CREATE US.
SHE NEEDED TEST SUBJECTS
FOR A SACRED ART
SHE WAS EXPERIMENTING WITH
THAT COULD RESURRECT THE DEAD.
WE RECEIVED OUR CALLINGS
WHEN WE WERE FIVE,
EARLIER THAN OTHER CHILDREN.
OUR JOB WAS TO KILL EACH OTHER.
WE WERE GIVEN LITTLE SWORDS
THAT LOOKED LIKE TOYS.
THEN, WE’D PAIR OFF AND
TAKE TURNS STABBING EACH OTHER.
( singers vocalizing )
♪
( blade stabs )
Fizel: AT FIRST, ADMINISTRATOR’S
ATTEMPTS AT RESURRECTION WERE--
HOW SHALL I SAY? NOT SO GOOD.
THERE WERE SOME CHILDREN
WHO EXPLODED
AND OTHERS WHO ENDED UP
AS WEIRD BLOBS OF FLESH.
AND STILL OTHERS WHO RETURNED,
BUT WERE DIFFERENT.
Linel: WE WERE BEING
RESURRECTED OVER AND OVER,
BUT WE DIDN’T LIKE
DYING IN PAIN,
SO THE TWO OF US RESEARCHED
HOW TO KILL WITH ONE STRIKE.
WE FOUND THAT IF
WE KILLED CLEANLY,
IT DIDN’T HURT AS MUCH
AND THE ODDS OF BEING
SUCCESSFULLY RESURRECTED
WERE HIGHER,
BUT...
THE PROBLEM WAS DECIDING
WHICH STRIKE WORKED THE BEST.
WE NARROWED IT DOWN
TO LOPPING OFF THE HEAD
OR A QUICK STAB TO THE HEART.
THEY BOTH WORKED EQUALLY WELL.
IN THE END, THOUGH,
ADMINISTRATOR DECIDED
IT WAS TOO DIFFICULT
TO MASTER THE SACRED ART
OF RESURRECTION.
WE WERE ABOUT EIGHT YEARS OLD
WHEN SHE ABANDONED
THE EXPERIMENT.
WHEN IT STARTED,
THERE WERE 30 OF US,
BUT ZEL AND I
WERE THE ONLY SURVIVORS.
( Eugeo gasping )
Linel: THEN ADMINISTRATOR
MADE A SPECIAL EXCEPTION
AND MADE US INTEGRITY KNIGHTS.
WELL, TO A CERTAIN DEGREE.
SHE SAID
WE HADN’T LEARNED ENOUGH
TO GO ON GUARD DUTY
LIKE THE OTHER KNIGHTS,
SO WE’VE BEEN STUDYING
THE LAWS AND SACRED ARTS
WITH THE OTHER APPRENTICES
FOR THE PAST TWO YEARS.
TO BE HONEST,
WE’RE TIRED OF IT.
Fizel: EARLIER TODAY,
WE WERE DISCUSSING WAYS
TO EARN OUR DRAGONS
AND DIVINE OBJECTS MORE QUICKLY.
WE HEARD THAT MINIONS
FROM THE DARK TERRITORY
HAD INFILTRATED THE CATHEDRAL,
SO WE THOUGHT, IF WE COULD
CAPTURE AND EXECUTE THEM
BEFORE THE OTHER KNIGHTS COULD,
IT WOULD SHOW ADMINISTRATOR
HOW CAPABLE WE WERE
AND SHE WOULD MAKE US
FULL-FLEDGED KNIGHTS,
SO WE WAITED ON THE STAIRS.
Linel: WE’RE TRULY SORRY
FOR USING POISON ON YOU.
IT WAS OUR ONLY OPTION.
YOU SEE,
WE WANTED TO BRING YOU
TO THE 50th FLOOR ALIVE,
IF POSSIBLE.
OH, AND WHEN WE DO GET THERE,
DON’T YOU WORRY.
FIZEL AND I
ARE REALLY GOOD AT KILLING.
IT WON’T HURT AT ALL.
( both groan )
♪
Linel: WELL, WELL, IF IT ISN’T
ALL FOUR OF THE WHIRLING BLADES,
AS WELL AS VICE COMMANDER
FANATIO SYNTHESIS TWO.
Fizel: THE WHOLE SENATE
MUST BE IN A PANIC.
WHY ELSE
WOULD THEY ASK YOU HERE,
FANATIO OF
THE HEAVEN-PIERCING BLADE?
Fanatio: YOU APPRENTICES
SHOULD NOT BE ON THE BATTLEFIELD
WITH HONORABLE KNIGHTS.
( Fizel laughs )
NOW, THAT IS FUNNY!
IT’S BECAUSE YOU BRING HONOR
AND TRADITION INTO BATTLE,
THAT YOU SO-CALLED
MIGHTY INTEGRITY KNIGHTS LOST
NOT ONCE, BUT TWICE!
BUT DON’T YOU WORRY.
AS YOU CAN SEE,
WE CAUGHT THE INTRUDERS,
AND WE’LL MAKE SURE
THE REPUTATION OF THE KNIGHTS
WON’T BE SULLIED ANY FURTHER.
YOU CAN COUNT ON THAT.
Linel: SHE’S RIGHT!
WE’RE GOING TO DECAPITATE
THESE SINNERS
RIGHT HERE AND NOW,
SO WATCH CLOSELY, AND MAKE SURE
TO GIVE AN ACCURATE REPORT
TO THE PONTIFEX.
YOU ARE HONORABLE KNIGHTS,
AFTER ALL.
WE TRUST YOU
NOT TO STEAL OUR CREDIT.
THAT WOULD BE COWARDLY.
♪
( girls gasp )
Linel: NO FAIR.
Fizel: I CAN’T...
( both moan )
( Linel shuddering )
( Eugeo groans )
Kirito: IT’LL WEAR OFF
IN A MINUTE.
AS SOON AS YOU CAN MOVE
YOUR LIPS AGAIN,
RECITE YOUR PERFECT WEAPON ART,
BUT KEEP IT DOWN.
THIS AIN’T GONNA WORK
IF THE KNIGHTS HEAR.
WHEN IT’S READY TO GO,
HANG ON TO IT A BIT.
WAIT FOR MY SIGNAL.
I’M SURE YOU’RE WONDERING,
HOW IN THE WORLD CAN I MOVE?
YOU GAVE YOURSELVES AWAY.
YOU SAID ALL THE MONKS,
NUNS, AND APPRENTICES
WERE ORDERED
TO STAY IN THEIR ROOMS,
AND IF YOU’RE A MONK,
NUN, OR APPRENTICE,
THERE’S NO WAY YOU’D
DISOBEY THE CHURCH’S ORDER.
BUT YOU WEREN’T IN YOUR ROOMS.
YOU WERE LOOKING FOR US,
SO THAT MEANT YOU GUYS
WEREN’T REAL APPRENTICES.
I ALSO NOTICED THOSE SCABBARDS
YOU GOT ARE MADE OF RUBY OAK.
THEY USE THAT WOOD
TO HOLD SWORDS
MADE OF TOXIC RUBERYL STEEL.
WHY? ’CAUSE IT’S THE ONLY THING
THAT WON’T ROT
AGAINST THE BLADE.
THERE’S NO WAY
YOU’D HAVE SOMETHING LIKE THAT
IF YOU WERE SISTERS-IN-TRAINING.
THAT’S WHY I STARTED RECITING
A POISON-NEUTRALIZING ART
BEFORE YOU GOT NEAR US.
IT TOOK A WHILE TO KICK IN,
BUT WHAT CAN YOU DO?
THERE’S MORE TO STRENGTH
THAN BEIN’ FAST WITH A SWORD.
( Fizel gasping )
( blades slice )
( both sigh )
DON’T WORRY. I WON’T KILL YOU.
I’M GONNA TEACH YOU
A LESSON TODAY.
YOU’RE GONNA WATCH THESE KNIGHTS
YOU MADE FUN OF FIGHT
AND SEE WHAT REAL STRENGTH’S
ALL ABOUT.
( footsteps receding )
♪
SORRY FOR THE WAIT,
VICE COMMANDER FANATIO.
MY NAME’S KIRITO,
THE SWORDSMAN!
♪
( yells )
Woman: HOW DARE YOU DO BATTLE
WITH THE VICE COMMANDER?!
THE FOUR WHIRLING BLADES
ARE YOUR OPPONENTS HERE!
TURN AND FACE US!
Fanatio: HOLD YOUR POSITION.
THIS ONE IS MINE.
Woman: AS YOU WISH.
Fanatio: SYSTEM CALL.
ENHANCE ARMAMENT!
( Kirito growls )
( yells )
( groans )
( sighs )
( gasps )
Eugeo: KI--
MY VOICE.
IT’S BACK!
SYSTEM CALL.
( Kirito groaning )
Fanatio: CRIMINAL OR NO,
IF YOU LIVED IN CENTORIA,
YOU SHOULD KNOW
WHAT A MIRROR IS.
IT IS AN INSTRUMENT
CAPABLE OF REFLECTING
SOLUS’S LIGHT COMPLETELY.
LONG AGO, THE PONTIFEX GATHERED
1,000 ENORMOUS MIRRORS
TO FOCUS SOLUS’S
MIDSUMMER LIGHT,
CREATING A PURE, WHITE FLAME.
IT WAS SO HOT,
IT MELTED A HUMAN-SIZED BOULDER
WITHIN MINUTES.
THE PONTIFEX,
USING HER HOLY SKILLS,
FUSED THE 1,000 MIRRORS
TOGETHER,
THEN HONED THEM
TO CREATE A MAGNIFICENT SWORD...
♪
THIS SWORD,
THE HEAVEN-PIERCING BLADE.
KNOW THIS. YOUR STOMACH AND FOOT
WERE PUNCTURED
BY THE GLORIOUS POWER
OF THE SUN GOD, SOLUS.
Kirito: IT REFLECTS
THE SUN’S ENERGY.
Fanatio: NOW, SINNER,
PREPARE TO MEET YOUR END.
Kirito: DISCHARGE!
( groans )
( Fanatio groans )
( gasps )
( both gasp )
♪
Fanatio:
DON’T YOU DARE LOOK AT ME.
YOUR EYES
ARE LACED WITH DISDAIN,
JUST LIKE THE COMMANDER’S!
YOU MEN THINK MY GENDER
AFFECTS THE QUALITY OF MY SKILL.
EVEN SINNERS DENY ME RESPECT!
I COMMAND YOU
TO FIGHT ME IN EARNEST!
I AM A KNIGHT,
AN INTEGRITY KNIGHT!
( Kirito groaning )
( Fanatio groaning )
Kirito: I GET IT.
YOUR SWORD AND SKILL,
IT’S A COVER.
THEY LET YOU STAND BACK
AND FIRE SHOTS
AND HIDE THE FACT
YOU’RE A WOMAN.
AIN’T THAT RIGHT, LADY FANATIO?!
Fanatio: HOW DARE YOU?!
Kirito: JUST SO YOU KNOW,
THE REASON I LOOKED
SO SHOCKED BEFORE,
IT WASN’T ’CAUSE YOU’RE A WOMAN.
IT’S ’CAUSE,
WHEN YOU LOST YOUR HELMET,
YOU LOST ALL YOUR NERVE.
I KNOW WHY YOU HIDE YOUR FACE
UNDER THAT HELMET.
IF ANYONE HERE’S GOT A PROBLEM
WITH YOU BEIN’ A WOMAN,
IT’S YOU.
( Fanatio growls )
SILENCE! YOU WRETCH!
I SHALL KILL YOU!
Kirito: YOU WANNA TRY, GO AHEAD!
I KNOW WHAT IT’S LIKE
TO FIGHT AND LOSE TO WOMEN,
AND YOU KNOW WHAT?
I NEVER HELD BACK FOR THEM,
AND I WON’T FOR YOU! ( grunts )
( growls )
♪
( woman vocalizing )
( Kirito sighs )
( Fanatio chuckles )
Eugeo: NO WAY.
( both yell )
Fanatio: I WAS WRONG.
♪
YOU ARE DIFFERENT.
ALTHOUGH YOU MAY BE A SINNER,
YOU ARE QUITE UNLIKE
THE OTHER MEN
I HAVE FOUGHT BEFORE.
NONE OF THEM HAD YOUR SPIRIT.
THEIR ATTACKS
ALL LACKED CONVICTION
ONCE THEY SAW
MY DETESTABLE FACE.
Kirito: "DETESTABLE"? OKAY...
THEN HOW COME YOU COMB YOUR HAIR
AND PUT ON LIPSTICK
IF YOU WEAR A HELMET?
YOU DON’T DO IT FOR YOURSELF.
THAT’S FOR SURE.
( Fanatio scoffs )
♪
Kirito: YOU’RE BITTER,
’CAUSE YOU CAN’T HAVE
THE PERSON YOU LOVE,
AND YOU KNOW WHY?
IT’S ’CAUSE THE CHURCH
AND THE PONTIFEX SAY YOU CAN’T.
WELL, I’M HERE TO DESTROY ’EM
AND FREE EVERYONE
FROM THEIR TYRANNY!
Fanatio: I CAN TELL
YOU ARE NO AGENT OF DARKNESS,
AS THE PRIME MINISTER CLAIMED.
REGARDLESS, YOU ARE
STILL EXTREMELY DANGEROUS.
YOU WOULD DISRUPT THE CHURCH
AND THE KNIGHTHOOD,
NOT JUST WITH YOUR SWORD,
BUT WITH YOUR WORDS.
YOU ALSO PUT
THE HUMAN EMPIRE IN PERIL,
AND THAT, SIR,
IS A KNIGHT’S DUTY TO PROTECT.
YOU SPEAK THE TRUTH,
BUT I AM OBLIGED TO DEFEAT YOU,
EVEN IF IT SULLIES
MY PRIDE AS A KNIGHT!
HIDDEN LIGHT
OF THE HEAVEN-PIERCING BLADE,
CAST OFF YOUR SHACKLES!
RELEASE RECOLLECTION!
( Kirito groaning )
( gasps )
( woman gasps )
Kirito: YOU IDIOT.
( gasps )
YOU’RE GONNA KILL US ALL!
Eugeo: NOW’S MY CHANCE,
MY ONLY CHANCE!
ENHANCE ARMAMENT!
( woman gasping )
( grunts ) NO--
Eugeo: BLUE ROSE! BLOOM!
( Fanatio gasps )
DAMN THAT BRAT!
( gasps )
( Kirito groans )
Eugeo: KIRITO!
ARE YOU HURT?! DON’T MOVE!
I’LL HEAL YOU!
Kirito: I’M FINE!
DON’T LET UP! KEEP AT IT!
SHE’S TOUGH.
THIS AIN’T ENOUGH TO STOP HER!
( groans )
SYSTEM CALL.
( Eugeo gasps )
♪
YOU KNIGHTS,
YOU’RE ALL THE SAME!
YOU’RE ALL HEARTLESS!
STOP FIGHTING!
STOP OR DIE!
( gasps )
IT’S NO USE.
I CAN’T WIN.
I CAN’T BEAT HER.
Kirito: YOU’RE LETTING HATE
GET THE BETTER OF YOU, EUGEO.
STOP IT.
YOU DIDN’T COME THIS FAR
’CAUSE YOU HATED
THE INTEGRITY KNIGHTS, DID YOU?
YOU’RE HERE TO GET ALICE BACK.
YOU’RE HERE ’CAUSE YOU LOVE HER.
BUT GUESS WHAT.
THAT INTEGRITY KNIGHT
OVER THERE,
SHE FEELS JUST AS STRONG
ABOUT HER DUTY,
AND I’M NO DIFFERENT.
I WANNA PROTECT
EVERYONE IN THIS WORLD--
YOU, ALICE,
EVEN THIS KNIGHT.
WE’RE SO CLOSE,
AND WE CAN’T AFFORD
TO GIVE UP NOW.
AIN’T THAT RIGHT, EUGEO?
( Eugeo sighs )
Kirito: ENHANCE ARMAMENT!
Singer: ♪ OH, EVERYTHING
TURNS TO ASH, TO ASH ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ AND EVERYTHING
TURNS TO DUST, TO DUST ♪
( singing in Japanese )
♪ FORGET-ME-NOT ♪